Guide to the Dennis Cooper Papers ca. 1970-2002 MSS 085
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Biographical material and personal correspondence
  - Subseries A: Biographical material
    - Grove Weidenfeld and Kresge Cultural Intersections Program, reading by Denis Cooper, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 788)
    - Don't Make Me Say Things That Will Hurt You, undated (Box 10, Folder 789)
    - Poetry Gone Gay (Box 10, Folder 790)
    - Zine party and reading, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 791)
    - Reading: poetry gone gay, undated (Box 11, Folder 792)
    - Readings: "Get it in writing", 1983 (Box 11, Folder 793)
    - Readings: Them, undated (Box 11, Folder 794)
    - Basement, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 795)
    - Basement, Cooper and Lenore Champagne, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 796)
    - Between C and D, two readings, undated (Box 11, Folder 797)
    - ABC NO RIO benefit for Little Caesar Press, undated (Box 11, Folder 798)
    - PS 122, undated (Box 11, Folder 799)
    - Beyond Baroque. Cooper, David Trinidad, Ed Smith, Benjamin Weissman, Amy Gerstler, undated (Box 11, Folder 800)
    - Poetry Resource Center of Michigan, LINES: National Writers Series. Dennis Cooper and Eileen Myles, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 801)
    - Poetry Project at St. Mark's Church., undated (Box 11, Folder 802)
    - Lambda Rising reading, Dennis Cooper and Brad Gooch, undated (Box 11, Folder 803)
    - Stitching One World Poetry, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 804)
    - An Evening of Poetry, Olga Broumas and Dennis Cooper, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 805)
    - The Poetry Project, Eileen Myles' introduction of Dennis Cooper, undated (Box 11, Folder 806)
    - Sound Off: A Benefit for Performance Space 122, undated (Box 11, Folder 807)
    - Gay and Lesbian pride events, Boston, undated (Box 11, Folder 808)
    - Brad Gooch and Dennis Cooper in Boston, undated (Box 11, Folder 809)
    - Opinionated Survey featuring Dennis Cooper, undated (Box 11, Folder 810)
    - Gay and Lesbian Literature: A Different Light, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 811)
    - Performance Space 122, undated (Box 11, Folder 812)
    - The Poetry Project, Ted Berrigan Memorial, undated (Box 11, Folder 813)
    - Oranges Sardines Gallery, Cooper and Ed Smith, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 814)
    - The Mercury Arts Center, undated (Box 11, Folder 815)
    - Art Talk Art, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 816)
    - Cooper on De Sade, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 817)
    - Outwrite, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 818)
    - Gay and Lesbian Literary Salon. UCLA Extension, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 819)
    - Reviews, undated (Box 11, Folder 820)
    - Reviews, undated (Box 11, Folder 821)
    - Reviews, undated (Box 11, Folder 822)
    - Reviews, undated (Box 11, Folder 823)
    - Reviews, undated (Box 11, Folder 824)
    - Thompson, KD (grandmother), newspaper article about Thompson, undated (Box 11, Folder 825)
  - Subseries B: Personal Correspondence
    - Correspondence, early rejection letters, undated (Box 11, Folder 826)
    - Correspondence, A-Bo, undated (Box 11, Folder 827)
    - Correspondence, Br-Gr, undated (Box 11, Folder 828)
    - Correspondence, Gr-Ho, undated (Box 11, Folder 829)
    - Correspondence, Ke-Ma, undated (Box 11, Folder 830)
    - Correspondence, Mc-No, undated (Box 11, Folder 831)
    - Correspondence, Pe-St, undated (Box 11, Folder 832)
    - Correspondence, Su-Yo, undated (Box 11, Folder 833)
    - Correspondence, unidentified correspondents, undated (Box 11, Folder 834)
- Series V: Beyond Baroque
  - Beyond Baroque, correspondence, undated (Box 11, Folder 835)
  - Ted Berrigan Reading, undated (Box 11, Folder 835a)
  - Beyond Baroque, readings, undated (Box 11, Folder 836)
  - Reviews, undated (Box 11, Folder 836a)
  - Beyond Baroque, writing workshops and press, undated (Box 11, Folder 837)
  - Writing Workshop, undated (Box 11, Folder 838)
  - Photos, undated (Box 11, Folder 838a)
- Series VI: Little Caesar Magazine/ Little Caesar Press
  - Subseries A: Little Caesar Magazine
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 11, Folder 838b)
    - Invoice/Receipts, undated (Box 11, Folder 839)
    - Little Caesar Press Catalogue, undated (Box 11, Folder 840)
    - Reviews, undated (Box 11, Folder 841)
    - Reviews, undated (Box 11, Folder 841a)
    - Press/Production, undated (Box 11, Folder 842)
    - Little Caesar Press Book Reviews, undated (Box 11, Folder 843)
    - Transparencies, undated (Box 11, Folder 844)
    - Photos, undated (Box 11, Folder 845)
    - Photos/negatives, undated (Box 11, Folder 846)
    - Sales Records, undated (Box 11, Folder 847)
    - Poetry Flash, undated (Box 11, Folder 848)
    - Tax Records, undated (Box 11, Folder 849)
    - Mock-ups or Issue #3, undated (Box 11, Folder 850)
    - Mock-ups Issue #4, undated (Box 11, Folder 851)
    - Mock-ups Issue #5--notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 852)
    - Mock-ups Issue #5, undated (Box 11, Folder 853)
    - Mock-ups Issue #6, undated (Box 12, Folder 854)
    - Mock-ups Issue #6, undated (Box 12, Folder 855)
    - Mock-ups Issue #7, undated (Box 12, Folder 856)
    - Mock-ups Issue #8, undated (Box 12, Folder 857)
    - Mock-ups Issue #10, undated (Box 12, Folder 858)
    - Mock-ups Issue #10, undated (Box 12, Folder 859)
    - Mock-ups Issue #11, undated (Box 12, Folder 860)
    - Mock-ups Issue #11-cont, undated (Box 12, Folder 861)
    - Mock-ups Issue #11-cont, undated (Box 12, Folder 862)
    - Mock-ups Issue #11-cont, undated (Box 12, Folder 863)
    - Mock-ups Issue #11-cont, undated (Box 12, Folder 864)
    - Mock-ups Issue #11-cont, undated (Box 12, Folder 865)
    - Mock-ups Issue #11-cont, undated (Box 12, Folder 866)
  - Subseries B: Little Caesar Press
    - Blakeston, Oswell. Journies End in Young.--cover, undated (Box 12, Folder 871)
    - Blakeston, Oswell. Journies End in Young Man's Meeting.--mock-ups, undated (Box 12, Folder 872)
    - Clark, Tom. The End of the Line--mock-ups, undated (Box 12, Folder 875)
    - Coming Attractions--correspondence and photos, undated (Box 12, Folder 876)
    - Coming Attractions--pp 1-60, undated (Box 12, Folder 877)
    - Coming Attractions--pp 61-116, undated (Box 12, Folder 878)
    - Coming Attractions--pp 118-158, undated (Box 12, Folder 879)
    - Coming Attractions--mss and cover art, undated (Box 12, Folder 880)
    - Coming Attractions--photos, undated (Box 12, Folder 881)
    - Coming Attractions--reviews, undated (Box 12, Folder 882)
    - Coming Attractions--Poetry Project Newsletter, undated (Box 12, Folder 883)
    - Dlugos, Tim. Je Suis Ein Americano.--mock-ups, undated (Box 12, Folder 885)
    - Koertge, Ron. Sex Object--mock-ups, undated (Box 12, Folder 888)
    - The Greatest Hits 1976-82. Manuscript, undated (Box 12, Folder 892)
    - Greatest Hits--cont, undated (Box 12, Folder 893)
    - Greatest Hits--cont, undated (Box 12, Folder 894)
    - Greatest Hits--cont, undated (Box 12, Folder 895)
    - Little Caesar Press--Cover, undated (Box 12, Folder 900)
    - Little Caesar Press--misc, undated (Box 12, Folder 901)
    - Malanga, Gerard, undated (Box 12, Folder 902)
    - Michael Lally Interviews--mock-ups, undated (Box 12, Folder 903)
    - Michael Lally--cont, undated (Box 12, Folder 904)
    - Rimbaud, Arthur, undated (Box 12, Folder 906)
- Series VII: Media
  Series contains all media for the Dennis Cooper Papers.
  - Subseries A: Video Recordings - Access Copies
    There are currently no video access copies available. Please check with Fales archivist.
  - Subseries B: Video Recordings - Originals
    Subseries contains all original video material.
    - [1.] -- Drugstore Cowboy: Dailies #45-50 [2.] -- Gus Van Sant shorts., 6 Oct. 1988 (Box 13, Folder ID: 085.0001)
      General note
      Format: VHS
      TRT: 00:50:00
    - Drugstore Cowboy. Director's Cut., 1989 (Box 13, Folder ID: 085.0002)
      TRT: [Unknown]
    - Frisk (Workprint). Dir. Todd Verow. Strand Releasing., 11 Jul.1994 (Box 13, Folder ID: 085.0003)
      TRT: 01:25:27
    - Frisk. Dir. Todd Verow. Strand Releasing., 1996 (Box 13, Folder ID: 085.0004)
      TRT: 01:28:19
    - [1.] -- Knife/Tape/Rope (5/12/89) [2.] -- Hole: The Spoken Word (Danspace)., [1.] 12 May 1989 [2.] Undated (Box 13, Folder ID: 085.0005)
    - "Knife/Tape/Rope." Ishmael Houston-Jones., 24 Nov. 1990 (Box 13, Folder ID: 085.0006)
    - Mitch Wilson. Broken Arrow Productions., Undated (Box 13, Folder ID: 085.0007)
    - "The Undead." LACE., 12 Sept.1990 (Box 13, Folder ID: 085.0008)
    - Excerpts from "The Undead"., 12 Sept.1990 (Box 13, Folder ID: 085.0009)
      TRT: 00:20:00
    - "The Undead." KCET. Studio Shoot.7 min./ "The Undead." KCET. Excerpts and Interviews/ A "The Undead." Live Excerpts.20 min., [1990] (Box 13, Folder ID: 085.0010)
  - Subseries C: Audio Recordings - Access Copies
    There are currently no audio access copies available. Please check with Fales archivist.
  - Subseries D: Audio Recordings - Originals
    Subseries contains all original audio material.
    - "Dennis Cooper." Interview by Ad Fransen. Passanten. VPRO. Dutch Radio., 21 Aug.1990 (Box 13, Folder ID: 085.0011)
      Format: audiocassette
    - "Dennis Cooper." Bookworm. KCRW 89.9. National Public Radio., 25 April 1994 (Box 13, Folder ID: 085.0012)
    - "Dennis Cooper." Summerstage. WNYC. National Public Radio., 14 Jul.1994 (Box 13, Folder ID: 085.0013)
    - "Dennis Cooper." Bookworm. KCRW 89.9. National Public Radio., 11 Jun.1997 (Box 13, Folder ID: 085.0014)
- Series VIII: Zines
  - about Dusty Springfield moves. San Francisco, CA: A silent Twins Production, n.d.. Abrupt Lane Edge. Minn., MN: Abrupt Lane Edge. #2, n.d.. Absolutely Zippo. Pinole, CA: Absolutely Zippo. #13, n.d.. Abuse. Allston, MA: Abuse. #2, n.d.. Ad/Vance. Arlington, VA: Ad/Vance. Spring 1993-Summer 1993. Vol. 1, Issues 3-4. Agony. Milwaukee, WI: Agony. #1, n.d.. (Box 14, Folder 922)
  - And Now I Devour You. Olympia, WA. N.d.. Angel of Death. Bronx, NY: Angel of Death. Summer 1990. #1. Amnesia. Los Angeles, CA: Amnesia. 1990 #1. And the Beat Goes On. Austin, TX: And the Beat Goes On. #2, n.d.. (Box 14, Folder 923)
  - Artpolice. Minn., MN: Artpolice. 7 Feb 1985; 31 Oct. 1986; July 1987; Dec. 1987; 1988; March 1989; (1990); (1990); (1990); 23 Oct. 1991; Vol. 18, #1 (1991); Summer 1991, Vol. 18/#2; 1991, #3; n.d.., 1985-1991 (Box 14, Folder 924)
  - Babyfish. Detroit, MI: Babyfish. N.d.. Bad Subjects. Berkeley, CA: Bad Subjects. March/April 1993, #5. Barbara's Psychic Anus. San Francisco, CA: Tongue-Fuck Productionz. N.d.. Bash. Broadville, Il.: Under Cover Comics. 1988 Ben is Dead. Hollywood, CA: Ben is Dead. March/April 1992, #18. Bed Pan Journal. N.P.. Summer 1992, #2. Better Homos and Gardens. West Hollywood, CA: Better Homos and Gardens. Spring 1992, #1., 1988-1993 (Box 14, Folder 925)
  - Bimbox. Toronto: Bimbox. Spring 1990, #1; Summer 1990. #2; n.d., #4; n.d., #5; Condensced n.d., #7. Black Crosses Graphics. Kennesaw, GA: Black Crosses Graphics. 1991, #1; 1991, #2., 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 926)
  - Boiled Angel. Largo, FL: Boiled Angel. N.d., #7; n.d., #8. Boy as Bomb. Chicago, Il: Boy as Bomb. N.d.. Boysville U.S.A.. Olympia, WA: Boysville U.S.A.. Spring 1988, Vol. 1/#1; July-Aug. 1988, Vol. 1/#2. Brains or Hardcore Punks Against Dead Guys. N.p.. 1990, #2. Brains: The Journal of Egghead Sexuality. San Francisco, B. Works. Summer 1990, Vol. 1/#1., 1988-1990 (Box 14, Folder 927)
  - Brane Skan. Los Angeles, CA: Brane Skan. 1991, #3. The Best of Look at Brock. Valencia, CA: Sub Prod.. April 1988, #3. Bullshit Monthly. New York: Bullshit Monthly. March 1990, #23; May/June 1990, #24. Bundle of Sticks. Minn, MN: Bundle of Sticks. Spring 1992, #5; Nov.-Dec. 1992, #7; n.d., #8. bunny butt. San Francisco, CA: bunnybutt. Spring 1994, #1., 1988-1994 (Box 14, Folder 928)
  - Campfire. San Francisco, CA: A Silent Twins Production. N.d., #1; n.d., #2. The Carnifex Network. Chicago, Il: The Carnifex Network. Feb. 1991, Vol. 1/#3. Chameleon. Melrose Pk., Il.: Action Printing. 1988; n.d., #2. Chaos Comix. N.p.. #19; n.d.., 1988-1991 (Box 14, Folder 929)
  - Children of the Void. Paramount, CA: Children of void. N.d.. Chimpanzee Waltz. Austin, TX: Raised by Wolves. 1990 Vol. 3 Collateral Damage. N.p.. N.d. Cometbus. Berkeley, CA: Cometbus. N.d.. #26. (Box 14, Folder 931)
  - Dead Jackie Susann Quarterly. New York: Dead Jackie Susann Quarterly. N.d.. Debbie and Dan's Queer Brunch. San Francisco, CA: Debbie and Dan. #1, n.d.. Dirty Plotte. By Julie Doucet. Montreal, Canada: Drawn and Quarterly Publications. March 1991. #2. Disney Vasectomy. Chicago, Il.: Jeff Tady. #1, 1992. Don=t Tell Jane and Frankie. N.p. N.d.. (Box 14, Folder 932)
  - Double Bill. N.p.: Bitch Nation Entertainment. 1993 #2, #3, n.d.. Dragzine West Hollywood, CA: Dragzine. 1991 no. 2 Dry Pocket. Richmond, IN: A Dry Pocket to Piss In. N.d. Dumb Bitch Deserves to Die N.p. 2nd printing. Feb. 1990. no.2, 1984-1991 (Box 14, Folder 933)
  - 88 Chins. Toronto: K.O.N.E.. Nov. 1988 #2, #3, #27. Exhausted Autumn. Los Angeles, CA: L.A.C.E.. 1991 Exquisite Corpse. N.p.: Dark Horse Comics. Green Issue 1990, Red Issue 1990, Yellow Issue 1990., 1988-1991 (Box 14, Folder 934)
  - Fabulous Babes. N.p., N.d. #2. Fag Rag. Baltimore, MD: Fag Rag. 1987 Fagazine. Detroit, MI.: Fagazine. N.d.. #1. Fagazine: A Fucking Queer Comic-Zine. West Hollywood, CA: Fagazine Press. 1991 Vol 1/#1. Faggot. San Francisco, CA: queer riot press. Feb. 1990 #3, n.d.. Farm 6. New York: Farm 6. Fall 1993. #6. Fear Comics. Toronto, Canada: Reactor Art Design. N.d.. Fertile La Toyah Jackson. Los Angeles, CA: Fertile La Toyah Jackson. Paris Issue. N.d., Harvest Issue, n.d.., 1987-1990 (Box 14, Folder 935)
  - Fist in Your Face. Toronto, Canada: Fist in Your Face. Fall 1988. #1, #2. Fran an Maable.. Roslyn, PA: Mailbox Books. N.d., #1. From Safety to Here. N.p.: Drew Blood Press. Winter 1992. Fuh Cole. Chicago, IL.: Fuh Cole. N.d. #4, #5. Fuzz Box. Montreal, Canada: Fuzz Box. N.d., 1988-1992 (Box 14, Folder 936)
  - Gary Monster Magazine. Toronto, Canada: Gary Monster Magazine. N.d. #5, n.d.. Gay. Toronto, Canada: Gay. Oct. 15, 1964. Vol1/#11. The Gentle Women of California. N.p.. #6, n.d.. Geraldine. San Francisco, CA: Geraldine. 1987 Great God Pan. San Francisco, CA: Great God Pan. #3. N.d.. Gubba Gub Comix. Madison, WI: Gubba Gub Comix. January 1988. #2, March 1988. #3. September 1988. #4, n.d., n.d.., 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 937)
  - Hand Turkey. Valencia, CA: Hand Turkey. 15 Nov. 1991 Vol. 2, no. 1 Happy. Austin, TX: Anathema enterprises. #7. N.d.. Help Others. N.p, n.d.. Hey Neeters! Belmont, CA: Saga Graphics. Sept. 1990 #6. Highschool Fag. Reading, MA: Highschool Fag. Dec. 1990 #2., 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 938)
  - Holy titclamps. Minneapolis, MN: Holy titclamps. Sept. 1989, #2; Dec. 1989, #3; Mar. 1990, #4; Summer 1990, #5; Winter 1991/1992, #9; Summer 1992, #10; Winter 1992/1993, #11; Summer 1993, #12; Feb. 1994, #13; Sept. 1995, #15., 1989-1995 (Box 14, Folder 939)
  - Homo. New York: Homo. Aug. 1990, Vol. 1, No. 1; Sept. 1990, Vol 1, No. 2. Homoammo. Berkeley, CA: Homoammo. 1994 Homoboy. N.p.. N.d.. Homogirl. N.p.. #2, n.d.. Homocore. San Francisco, CA: Homocore. Dec. 1989, #5; March 1990, #5 2; Winter/Spring 1991, #7., 1989-1994 (Box 14, Folder 940)
  - HOMOture. San Francisco, CA: HOMOture. Summer 1991, #1; #2, n.d.; #4, n.d.. Hoo-be-boo. Torrence, CA: Hoo-be-boo. #1, 1983. Hubba. N.p.. Winter 1993, #2. Hysteria. San Francisco, CA: Hysteria. Feb.-Mar. 1990 I was a beauty school drop-out. N.p.. N.d.. Impulse. River Falls, WI.. Fall 1989. #5. In Bra Straps. New York: Concrete Block in Your Face Then. N.d.. Inciting Desire. Santa Cruz, CA: Inciting Desire. 1991 #1., 1983-1991 (Box 14, Folder 941)
  - Intent to Kill. N.p.. March 1992. Vol. 1, Issue 1; July 1992, Vol. 1, Issue 2; Dec. 1992, Vol. 3/4. (Box 14, Folder 942)
  - Inward Monitor. Saunderstown, R.I.: Inward Monitor. N.d.. #3. IQ. N.p.. N.d.., undated (Box 14, Folder 943)
  - J.D.s. Ontario, Canada: J.D.s. N.d., #4; n.d.. Joezine. New York: joezine. N.d., Second Tissue. johnny tomorrow. Chicago, IL: Davey Houle. 1996 (Box 14, Folder 944)
  - King-Cat. DeKalb, IL: King-Cat. 1992, #33; 1993, #39; n.d., #40. King of the Fairies. Toronto, Canada: King of the Fairies. N.d., #1. Kiss! Kiss!...Bang! Bang! Norman, OK: Kiss! Kiss!...Bang! Bang! Feb. 1993, Premiere Issue., 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 945)
  - Lana's World. Eugene, OR: How Do You Spell It Productions. N.d.. #2. Life is a Joke. San Francisco, CA: Life is a Joke. Aug. 1993 #2. Liliane. N.p.. N.d.. #16. Little Skull's Bay-Bee. Hollywood,CA: Little Skull's Bay-Bee. 1989, #10; 1989, #12; 1990, #13; 1990, #14; 1990, #15;1991, #16;1991, #17; 1991, #18., 1989-1993 (Box 15, Folder 946)
  - Living in a Powder Keg and Givin= Off Sparks. Brooklyn, NY: Full Force Productions. June 1990. #7; Aug. 1990, #8; Nov. 1990, #9. (Box 15, Folder 947)
  - Madonna/Ho. N.p.. N.d.. Man Bag. Minneapolis, MN: Artpolice. 1991, No. 1 The Marc Lepine Memorial Scrapbook. Brooklyn, NY: Frank's Zine. Feb. 1990 milquetoast. San Francisco, CA: milquetoast. #1, n.d.; #2, n.d.. Mirage. N.p.: Mirage. Aug. 1994, Vol. #4/#32; May 1995, Vol. #4/#42. modern words. San Francisco, CA: modern words. Summer 1994, #1. Mr. Fix Goes Conjuring. N.p.. 1984 The Mundane Adventures of Dishman. Ontario, Canada: The Mundane Adventures of Dishman. 1985, #1; 1986, #2. My Comrade. New York: My Comrade. Spring 1990; Winter 1990; Winter 1991., 1990-1995 (Box 15, Folder 948)
  - Naked Teenagers That Fight Crime. Minneapolis, MN: Naked Teenagers that Fight Crime. 1993, #1. no external compulsion. Madison, WI: no external compulsion. #5. No Longer a Fanzine. Blackwood, NJ: No Longer a Fanzine. Fall 1992, #2; Summer 1993, #3. Now I Swallow Your Pants. Olympia, WA: Now I Swallow Your Pants. N.d., #2. Nude Erections. Los Angeles, CA: Nude Erections. 1985, #2., 1985-1993 (Box 15, Folder 949)
  - Oblivion. Mamaroneck, NY: Oblivion. Jan. 1990 #1. 198,000 Miles. San Diego, CA: Hold the Pickle Publications. 1992 P.C. Casualties. Ann Arbor, MI: P.C. Casualties. N.d.., 1990-1992 (Box 15, Folder 950)
  - Palookaville. Montreal, Canada: Palooka-ville. April 1991. No. 1 Pansy Beat. New York: Pansy Beat. 1990 1991 A Patriarchy's Nightmare. N.p.. N.d.. Pavement of Surface. San Francisco, CA: Pavement of Surface. March 1990. #4. Peace Oil for Rat Brain Comics. Hollywood, CA: Peace Oil for Rat Brain Comics. Aub. 1987 #8., 1987-1991 (Box 15, Folder 951)
  - Pettibon, Raymond. Superflux Pubs.: n.p.. N.d. I Will Sign Anything; 1991 Psing a Psalm; 1991 From a Tower; 1991 Hum a Hymn; 1991 Knocking on the Louvre; 1991 Watching Onan. Dear St. John, 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 952)
  - I'll Show You the World; 1991 The Author is the Medium; n.d. Dear St. John; n.d. Harlow Hair; 1990 Origin Issue; n.d. Thoughts, Sympathies, Prayers; n.d. Writ; 1980 Liz; 1989 Bluebeard's Boudoir; 1990, 1980-1990 (Box 15, Folder 953)
  - Philly Zine. Glassboro, NJ: Philly Zine. Summer 1992. #11. Piercing O.D.. Los Angeles, CA: Piercing O.D.. N.d.. Pocho Magazine. Berkeley, CA: Pocho Magazine. N.d.. Project 36-C. N.p.. N.d.. Pucky. N.p.. 1988 #2. Pumping Petunias. N.p.. N.d.. Punk Pals. Berkeley, CA: Punk Pals. Nov. 1990 #11., 1988-1991 (Box 15, Folder 954)
  - QT. Montreal, Canada: QT. March 1991. #1. Queer Zine Explosion. San Francisco, CA: Queer Zine Explosion. N.d.. #12. Quinceanera. Toronto, Canada: Quinceanera. 1996, 1991-1996 (Box 15, Folder 955)
  - Scream Box. Los Angeles, CA: Scream Box. Nov. 1990 #1. Scab. Toronto, Canada: Scab. N.d.. #2; n.d.. Second Guess. Reno, NV: Second Guess. Summer 1993. #7. The Shitkickickin= Kid. Oregon, Ill.: Metalstorm. # 3. #6. Shut Up Little Man. San Francisco, CA: Tedium House Publications. 1992, 1990-1992 (Box 15, Folder 958)
  - Soft Tar. N.p.: Soft Tar Communications. 1994 Spawn of Satan. San Francisco, CA: S.O.S.. No. 1 Spunk. Los Angeles, CA: Spunk. 1994 (Box 15, Folder 960)
  - Staight to Hell: Archives of the American Academy of Homosexual Research. New York: A.A.A.H.R..Vol. 1: 45-52, undated (Box 15, Folder 961)
  - Staight to Hell: Archives of the American Academy of Homosexual Research. New York: A.A.A.H.R..Vol. 1: 53-54, 57-58. Vol. 2: 1-2., undated (Box 15, Folder 962)
  - Strange Looking Exile. Minneapolis, MN: Strange Looking Exile. #1, #2, #4. Swish! Toronto, Canada: J.D.'s. No. 8 1991 SWSII San Francisco, CA: SWSll. 1993-94. Su Madre. N.p.. Premiere ish, n.d.; two ish, n.d.. Superfly. Bensenville, IL: Mike Hunt Comix. #1. 1993 Super Hate Jr.. Brooklyn, NY: Super Hate Jr.. 1989, 1989-1994 (Box 15, Folder 963)
  - Tantrum. San Francisco, CA: Tantrum. #2. N.d.. Summer 1991. Spring 1993. Taste of Latex. San Francisco, CA: Taste of Latex. Vol. 1, No. 4 Winter 1990-91. Technocracy Blues. Royal Oak, MI: G.L. Barr Studio. No. 1 1991 Teen Meat. N.p: Teen Meat Publishing. Apr./May 1990, #4; Jul/Aug 1990, #5; Oct/Dec 1990, #6., 1990-1993 (Box 15, Folder 965)
  - Tellurian. Corvallis, Oregon: Tellurian. July 1973, #2. There But for the Grace of God. Norris, TN: There But for the Grace of God. N.d.. Thing. Chicago, Ill: Thing. Nov. 1989, No. 1; Apr. 1990, No. 2; Sex Issue, n.d.; Spring 1991, No. 4; Fall 1991, No. 5.; Fall 1992, No. 7, 1973-1992 (Box 15, Folder 966)
  - Three Dollar Bill. San Francisco, CA: Three Dollar Bill. 1991 #2. Throat Culture. Union, N.J.: Throat Culture. 1990 #2. Tommy! San Francisco, CA: Tommy! #5. Too Many Closets! N.p.. Drew Blood Press. Spring 1991., 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 967)
  - Tough-Horse. Melrose Park, Il.: Action Printing. N.d., #2, #3, #4. Traction. Milwaukee, WI: Traction. No. 2, Spring 1991. Trash Compactor. Toronto, Canada: Trash Compactor. Winter 1990, Vol.2,4. True Tales. Austin, TX: No Joke Publications. Sept 1990. No. 7 Turkey hand. Valencia, CA: Hand Turkey. 1 Nov. 1991 No. 1, Vol. 1; 1 Dec. 1991 No. 1, #3., 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 968)
  - "Ventilator Blues." Philadelphia, PA: Ventilator Blues.Sept 1995. #2. (Box 15, Folder 969)
  - Whorezine. San Francisco, CA: Whorezine. Mar.1992. No.X. Wig Rodeo. N.p. N.d. (Box 15, Folder 969a)
  - whispering campaign. San Francisco, CA: whispering campaign. No.2, No.3, Hyper-Diary., undated (Box 15, Folder 970)
  - you can't hide your love forever. Birmingham, MI: YCHYLF. Winter 1990. Issue #4. (Box 15, Folder 971)
  - Zugang. San Francisco,CA: Zugang. #8., undated (Box 15, Folder 972)
  - Zine Fragments--misc., undated (Box 15, Folder 973)
- Series IX: Posters
  These materials are located in the map case.
  - David Foster Wallace. The Infinite Jest., undated (Box map case, Folder 974)
- Oversize Materials Series IV: Biographical Material and Personal Correspondence
  - Subseries A: Biographical material
    - Readings: Writers for Health, undated (Box 16, Folder 819a)
    - Readings: Poetry Project, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 819b)
    - Readings: Theoretical, undated (Box 16, Folder 819c)
    - Readings: Dennis Cooper and Dan Diamond read poetry., 1981 (Box 16, Folder 819)
    - Readings: Dennis Cooper and Leland Hickman, undated (Box 16, Folder 819e)
    - Readings: Cooper Reads Poems Before Your Eyes, undated (Box 16, Folder 819)
    - Readings: A men's valentines poetry reading, undated (Box 16, Folder 819g)
    - Readings: Benefit for ACT UP, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 819h)
    - press coverage of Cooper and Chris Lemminhart's wedding in LA, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 819i)
    - Readings: Soup, undated (Box 16, Folder 819j)
- Oversize Materials Series VI: Little Caesar Magazine/Little Caesar Press
  - Subseries A: Little Caesar Magazine
    - Mock-ups, issue #11, cover, undated (Box 16, Folder 867)
    - Mock-ups Issue #11 part 1, undated (Box 16, Folder 868)
    - Mock-ups Issue #11 part 2, undated (Box 16, Folder 869)
    - Mock-ups Issue #12, photos, undated (Box 16, Folder 870)
  - Subseries B: Little Caesar Press
    - Brainard, Joe. Nothing to Write Home About, undated (Box 17, Folder 873)
    - Britton, Donald. Italy, undated (Box 17, Folder 874)
    - Dlugos, Tim. Entre Nous., undated (Box 17, Folder 884)